today on eway censored Supernatural
Bible changes on YouTube this will be a
really short video today is the 8th of
January
2024 and I'm really excited to tell you
that my latest book has been published
and it's available on
Amazon this book is called the impostor
in the Bible and it is a selection of
verses from the Old Testament and the
New Testament about God that have
changed and what I've done in this book
it's 6x6 or you know 5.75 5 by
6 and essentially it begins with talking
about what's happening to the Bible the
Bible is supernaturally changing and I
go into some information about that and
I also have a Salvation page and I give
verses as to what Bible verses told us
about these lying signs and wonders and
then some more background information
about what's happening and then I
literally dive into verse after verse
after verse after
verse about God that's been
changed and they're clearly
altered and what I've done is with each
verse that I wanted to highlight this
change about God you'll find it's in
bold the particular word or words and
then I also noted the other changes that
I see and I
italicized those
words I did not go in and rewrite the
scripture
verses but anyone who has eyes to see
will clearly see that something is a and
I believe this
book allows for a very
concise concise examples as to how the
Bible is changing to prepare the way for
the Antichrist and these scripture
verses that I show are showing a God
that I do not know and probably for you
too at least I hope so because I don't
know about you but my Creator does not
hiss and that's one of the verses in the
Bible that's changed saying that the
Lord now
hisses or that his name is jealous or
that he's called that Holy thing those
are some examples those are three
examples of
how they've changed God in the Bible and
I say they we're talking about the
wicked ones and we know these are all
lying signs and wonders that we are
warned about and we're are warned that
the
Antichrist would pretend that he is God
that's exactly what's happening the
Lawless one is
fiercely at work because he knows his
hour is short but our Bibles have become
a weapon of the wicked one and I know
that's maybe be so shocking and painful
and horrifying to hear but I'm
beseeching you to search out the matter
to pray and fast and seek the
Lord so this is the book right here the
impostor in the Bible and I want to show
you just a screenshot from Amazon it's
$10 and essentially it shows how the
enemy or the impostor is what I'm
calling him because he's a counterfeit
right he's a counterfeit he's not the
real God he's a pretender a liar an
actor an
impostor and so his intention is to one
of course blaspheme God and we know he
was planning on doing this the Lord knew
this in 2 Thessalonians 2 and he's
pretending that he is God right now with
the intention of deceiving the church
and literally leading to a great falling
away that we were warned about and I'm
here to warn anyone who has ears to hear
that our bibles are supernaturally
changing we are
seeing grammar errors punctuation errors
word switches words removed copy and
paste versus new people um new and
modern words words
erased whole new chapters it's
unbelievable and it's clearly happening
there's zero doubt about this be a ban
search out the matter pray and fast and
seek the Lord and I hope these books
that I'm creating will be of benefit to
you as you're doing your research and of
course brothers and sisters you don't
need me to help you see all you need to
do is ask the Holy Spirit to show you
and open up your Bibles and start
researching this anyway may God keep you
safe and bless you in your journey of
Truth and let me know what you guys
think about this book and I look forward
to talking to you soon bye everyone